trouble is everyone's crazy
everyone's crazy but ladies you own it
yeah because when you call a woman crazy
they agree with you
try it call a woman crazy they just go i
know
i don't know you might be laughing sir
you have a mask over your mouth so it's
hard to tell what's going on back there
thank you buddy i appreciate it
uh yeah no it's just it's very hard to
be in a relationship ladies i i do think
you own crazy i think you're crazy
drivers i'll say that
that's just based on my own family like
i'm driving with my sister she's about
to go through red light as she does she
does
this go what are you doing she goes oh
there's a camera at this slice
i don't want to get a ticket
yeah i don't work at the dmv but i'm
pretty sure there's a facial recognition
software
i don't think there's a guy with a photo
like ah they outsmarted us again
this could be anyone it could be a dog
it could be the hamburglar
how about the license plate nah that
will never work
get a sketch artist in here we'll figure
this house
driver criticizes my driving right
because she was with me when i was in a
minor car accident miner i hit a parked
car
she goes yeah you're gonna do the right
thing right i was like yup i'll drive
away
she goes no you're gonna do the right
thing you're gonna leave a note i did i
left a note nude said my car is fine
how is the traffic in utah do you guys
have traffic
is it bad
how like is it really bad
traffic traffic is bad like when traffic
traffic can really change uh who you are
as a person
like especially like i'm i'm referring
to your traffic but any traffic like new
york city traffic is so bad it will make
you talk bad about people you never
thought you would talk bad about if they
mess up traffic you'll tear down anyone
i was in new york when the pope visited
i never thought i was going to talk
about about the boat
i did
they shut down every street in the world
for the pope's safety which is
ridiculous
have a little faith
[Laughter]
i'm assuming this is a
not an international audience
i'm just going by the the flag
is there a meeting after this
[Music]
i was like you know who's in my audience
because you really have to know
especially if it's international like
don't complain to russian people ever
even if you're friends with them they've
always had way tougher lives always
always right like i got a russian friend
named i don't like you to like complain
to her she always got a way worse life
story you know she was like yes ryan i
understand when it's 8 years old kgb
killed my whole family right in front of
me
but yes girl not texting you back very
sad
you